♪ 'Twas brillig, and the slithy toves ♪
♪ Did gyre and gimble in the wabe; ♪
♪ All mimsy were the borogoves, ♪
♪ And the mome raths outgrabe. ♪
♪ "Beware the Jabberwock, my son! ♪
♪ The jaws that bite, the claws that catch! ♪
♪ Beware the Jubjub bird, and shun ♪
♪ The frumious Bandersnatch!" ♪
♪ He took his vorpal sword in hand: ♪
♪ Long time the manxome foe he sought— ♪
♪ So rested he by the Tumtum tree, ♪
♪ And stood awhile in thought. ♪
♪ And as in uffish thought he stood, ♪
♪ The Jabberwock, with eyes of flame, ♪
♪ Came whiffling through the tulgey wood, ♪
♪ And burbled as it came! ♪
♪ One, two! One, two! And through and through ♪
♪ The vorpal blade went snicker-snack! ♪
♪ He left it dead, and with its head ♪
♪ He went galumphing back. ♪
(Alice) A mad tea-party...
There was a table set out under a tree in front of the house.
The March Hare and the Hatter were having tea at it.
A Dormouse was sitting between them, fast asleep.
The other two were using it as a cushion, resting their elbows on it.
They were talking right over its head.
*Very uncomfortable for the Dormouse...*
Only, as it's asleep, I suppose it doesn't mind.
The table was a large one, but the three were all crowded together at one corner of it.
No room! No room!
There's plenty of room!
She sat down in a large arm-chair at one end of the table.
Have some wine.
I don't see any wine.
There isn't any.
Then it wasn't very civil of you to offer it.